<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.muon</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Muon Package Manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">مدير ميون للحزم</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Xestor de paquetes Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Gestor de paquets Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestor de paquets Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Správce balíčků Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Muon-pakkehåndtering</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Muon-Paketverwaltung</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Διαχειριστής πακέτων Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Muon Package Manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Gestor de paquetes Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Tarkvarahaldur Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Muon pakete kudeatzailea</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Muon-paketinhallinta</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire de paquets Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Xestor de paquetes Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">मुआन पैकेज प्रबंधक</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Muon csomagkezelő</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Muon Package Manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Gestore di pacchetti Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Muon 패키지 관리자</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Muon paketų tvarkyklė</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Muon pakketbeheerder</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Muon pakkehandsamar</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie pakietami Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Gestor de Pacotes Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciador de pacotes Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Administratorul de pachete Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Диспетчер пакетов Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Správca balíkov Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Muon upravljalnik paketov</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Muon pakethanterare</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Програма для керування пакунками Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxMuon Package Managerxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Muon 软件包管理器</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Muon 軟體包管理器</name>
  <summary>Search, install and remove software packages</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">ثبّت حزم البرمجيّات واعرضها وابحث عنها</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Busca, instala y desanicia paquetes de software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Cerca, instal·la i elimina paquets de programari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Cerca, instal·la i elimina paquets de programari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Søg, installer og fjern softwarepakker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Software-Pakete suchen, installieren und entfernen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Αναζητήαστε, εγκαταστήστε και αφαιρέστε πακέτα λογισμικού</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Search, install and remove software packages</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Buscar, instalar y eliminar paquetes de software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Tarkvarapakettide otsimine, paigaldamine ja eemaldamine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Bilatu, instalatu eta kendu software paketeak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Etsi, asenna ja poista ohjelmistopaketteja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Chercher, installer et supprimer des paquets logiciels</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Buscar, instalar e retirar paquetes de software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">सॉफ्टवेयर पैकेज खोजें, सथापित करे व हटाएँ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Szoftvercsomagok keresése, telepítése és eltávolítása</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Mencari, menginstal, dan menghapus aket-paket perangkat lunak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Cerca, installa e rimuove i pacchetti software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">소프트웨어 패키지 검색, 설치, 삭제</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Software pakketten zoeken, installeren en verwijderen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Søk etter, installer og fjern programpakkar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wyszukuj, wgrywaj i usuwaj programy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Pesquisar, instalar e remover os pacotes de aplicações</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Pesquisa, instala e remove pacotes de software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Caută, instalează și elimină pachete software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Hľadanie, inštalácia a odstránenie softvérových balíkov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Išči, namesti in odstrani programske pakete</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Sök efter, installera och ta bort programvarupaket</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Пошук, встановлення і вилучення пакунків із програмним забезпеченням</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSearch, install and remove software packagesxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">搜尋、安裝或移除軟體包</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Manage applications and libraries installed on your system to the package level. Search, install and remove packages and inspect their versions and their dependencies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">إدارة التطبيقات والمكتبات المثبتة على نظامك حتى مستوى الحزمة. ابحث عن الحزم وقم بتثبيتها وإزالتها وفحص إصداراتها وتبعياتها.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Xestiona aplicaciones y biblioteques instalaes nel sistema a nivel de paquete. Busca, instala y desanicia paquetes ya inspeiciona les versiones y dependencies de so.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Gestiona les aplicacions i biblioteques instal·lades al sistema al nivell dels paquets. Cerca, instal·la i elimina paquets, així com les seves versions i dependències.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestiona les aplicacions i biblioteques instal·lades al sistema al nivell dels paquets. Cerca, instal·la i elimina paquets, així com les seues versions i dependències.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Håndter programmer og biblioteker som er installeret på dit system på pakkeniveau. Søg, installer og fjern pakker, og inspicer deres versioner og deres afhængigheder.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Verwalten Sie Anwendungen und Bibliotheken, die auf Ihrem System installiert sind, als Pakete. Suchen, installieren und entfernen Sie Pakete und überprüfen Sie deren Versionen und ihre Abhängigkeiten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Διαχειριστείτε εφαρμογές και βιβλιοθήκες εγκατεστημένες στο σύστημά σας σε επίπεδο πακέτων. Αναζητήαστε, εγκαταστήστε και αφαιρέστε πακέτα και επιθεωρείστε τις εκδόσεις και τις εξαρτήσεις τους.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Manage applications and libraries installed on your system to the package level. Search, install and remove packages and inspect their versions and their dependencies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Gestionar aplicaciones y bibliotecas instaladas en su sistema a nivel de paquetes. Buscar, instalar y eliminar paquetes e inspeccionar sus versiones y sus dependencias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Süsteemi paigaldatud rakenduste ja teekide haldamine tarkvarapakettide tasemel. Pakettide otsimine, paigaldamine ja eemaldamine ning nende versioonide ja sõltuvuste väljaselgitamine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Kudeatu paketeen mailan zure sisteman instalatutako aplikazioak eta liburutegiak. Bilatu, instalatu eta kendu paketeak eta ikuskatu haien bertsioak eta mendekotasunak.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Hallitse järjestelmääsi asennettuja sovelluksia ja kirjastoja pakettien tasolla. Etsi, asenna ja poista paketteja ja tutki niiden versioita ja riippuvuuksia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Gérer les applications et bibliothèques installées sur votre système, paquet par paquet. Chercher, installer et supprimer des paquets et inspecter leurs versions et leurs dépendances.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Xestionar aplicacións e bibliotecas instaladas no sistema a nivel de paquetes. Buscar, instalar e retirar paquetes e inspeccionar as súas versións e dependencias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Muonnal kezelheti a telepített alkalmazásait és programkönyvtárait. Kereshet, telepíthet és eltávolíthat csomagokat, illetve megnézheti a verzióikat és függőségeiket.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Mengelola aplikasi dan pustaka yang terinstal pada sistemmu terhadap level paket. Mencari, menginstal, dan menghapus paket-paket, dan mengamati versinya, dan ketergantungannya.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Gestisce le applicazioni e le librerie installate nel tuo sistema a livello di pacchetti. Cerca, installa e rimuove i pacchetti, e ispeziona la loro versione e le loro dipendenze.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">시스템에 설치된 프로그램과 라이브러리를 패키지 단위로 관리합니다. 패키지를 검색, 설치, 삭제하고 버전 및 의존성을 볼 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Op uw systeem geïnstalleerde toepassingen en bibliotheken beheren op het pakketniveau. Pakketten zoeken, installeren en verwijderen en hun versies en afhankelijkheden inspecteren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Handsam systemet sine program og bibliotek på pakkenivå. Søk etter, installer og fjern pakkar, og få informasjon om pakkeversjonar og -avhengnadar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Zarządzaj aplikacjami  i bibliotekami wgranymi na twoim systemie na poziomie pakietów. Wyszukuj, wgrywaj i usuwaj pakiety, a także sprawdzaj ich wersje i zależności.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Gerir as aplicações e bibliotecas instaladas no seu sistema ao nível de cada pacote. Pesquise, instale e remova os pacotes e inspeccione as suas versões e dependências.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciar os aplicativos e bibliotecas instaladas no seu sistema ao nível de cada pacote. Pesquise, instale e remova os pacotes e inspecione as suas versões e dependências.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Gestionează aplicații și biblioteci instalate în sistem la nivel de pachet. Caută, instalează și elimină pachete, precum și inspectează versiunile acestora și dependențele lor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Upravljajte aplikacije in knjižnice, nameščene na vašem sistemu na stopnji paketa. Iščite, nameščajte in odstranjujte pakete in pregledujte njihove verzije in njihove odvisnosti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Hantera program och bibliotek installerade på systemet på paketnivå. Sök efter, installera och ta bort paket, samt inspektera deras versioner och beroenden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Керуйте програмами і бібліотеками, встановленими у вашій системі, на рівні пакунків. Шукайте, встановлюйте та вилучайте пакунки, а також ознайомлюйтеся із версіями пакунків та їхніми залежностями.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxManage applications and libraries installed on your system to the package level. Search, install and remove packages and inspect their versions and their dependencies.xx</p>
    <p>Note: this does not include applications distributed through Snap or Flatpack. You may prefer Plasma-Discover, if what you are looking for is a Software Center.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">ملاحظة: هذا لا يشمل التطبيقات الموزعة من خلال Snap أو Flatpack. قد تفضل Plasma-Discover ، إذا كان ما تبحث عنه هو مركز برمجيات.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Nota: esto nun inclúi aplicaciones distribuyíes pente Snap o Flatpack. Quiciabes prefieras Plasma-Discover si lo que tas buscando ye un centru de software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Nota: això no inclou les aplicacions distribuïdes mitjançant Snap o Flatpack. Potser preferireu el Plasma-Discover, si esteu cercant un Centre de programari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Nota: això no inclou les aplicacions distribuïdes mitjançant Snap o Flatpack. Potser preferireu el Plasma-Discover, si esteu cercant un Centre de programari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Bemærk: det inkluderer ikke programmer som distribueres gennem Snap eller Flatpack. Hvis du leder efter et softwarecenter, så vil du måske foretrække at bruge Plasma-Discover.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Hinweis: Dies gilt nicht für Anwendungen, die über Snap oder Faltpack verteilt werden. Sie sollten Plasma-Discover benutzen, wenn Sie ein Software-Verwaltungsprogramm suchen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Σημείωση: Αυτό δεν περιλαμβάνει εφαρμογές που διανέμονται με Snap ή Flatpack. Ίσως προτιμάτε το Plasma-Discover, αν αυτό που αναζητάτε είναι ένα Κέντρο Λογισμικού.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Note: this does not include applications distributed through Snap or Flatpack. You may prefer Plasma-Discover, if what you are looking for is a Software Centre.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Nota: esto no incluye las aplicaciones distribuidas mediante Snap o Flatpack. Es posible que prefiera usar Plasma-Discover en el caso de que esté buscando un centro de software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Märkus: see ei hõlma rakendusi, mida levitatakse Snapi või Flatpacki kaudu. Sellise tarkvarakeskuse soovi korral võiks vaadata Plasma-Discoveri poole.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Oharra: honek ez ditu barneratzen Snap edo Flatpack bidez banatutako aplikazioak. Agian nahiago izango duzu Plasma-Discover, bilatzen duzuna Software Gune bat bada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Huomaa: Tähän eivät sisälly Snapin tai Flatpackin kautta levitetyt ohjelmat. Jos etsit ohjelmistokeskusta, Plasma Discover voi olla mitä etsit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Remarque : cela n'inclut pas les applications distribuées via Snap ou Flatpack. Si vous cherchez un centre de logiciels, vous préférerez peut-être utiliser Plasma-Discover.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Nota: isto non inclúe aplicacións distribuídas mediante Snap ou Flatpack. Pode que prefira Plasma Discover, se o que busca é un centro de software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Fontos tudnia, hogy a Muon nem kezeli a Snapen vagy Flatpacken terjesztett alkalmazásokat. Ha egy szoftverközpont jellegű alkalmazást keres, a Plasma-Discovert érdemes kipróbálnia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Catatan: ini tidak termasuk aplikasi yang didistribusikan melalui Snap atau Flatpack. Kamu mungkin lebih menyukai Plasma-Discover, jika apa yang kamu cari adalah sebuah Pusat Software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Nota: questo non include le applicazioni distribuite attraverso Snap o Flatpack. Potresti preferire Plasma-Discover se stai cercando un Software Center.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">메모: Snap이나 Flatpack으로 설치된 프로그램은 표시되지 않습니다. 소프트웨어 센터를 찾고 있다면 Plasma 발견을 사용해 보십시오.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Opmerking: dit houdt geen toepassingen in gedistribueerd via Snap of Flatpack. U zou de voorkeur kunnen geven aan Plasma-Discover, als wat u zocht een Softwarecentrum is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Merk: Dette er ikkje medrekna program distribuert gjennom Snap eller Flatpak. Viss du ser etter eit programvaresenter, kan det hende du føretrekkjer programmet Discover.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Uwaga: Nie uwzględnia to aplikacji rozpowszechnianych przez Snap lub Flatpack. Do tego możesz chcieć użyć Odkrywcy Plazmy, jeśli to czego szukasz jest ośrodkiem programów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Nota: isto não inclui as aplicações distribuídas pelo Snap ou Flatpack. Poderá preferir o Plasma-Discover, se o que precisa é um Centro de Aplicações.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Observação: Isto não inclui os aplicativos distribuídos pelo Snap ou Flatpack. Você poderá preferir o Plasma-Discover, se precisar de uma Central de Aplicativos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Notă: aceasta nu include aplicații distribuite prin Snap sau Flatpack. Ați putea prefera Plasma Discover dacă ceea ce căutați e un centru de aplicații.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Opomba: to ne vključuje aplikacij, distribuiranih prek portalov Snap ali Flatpack. Morda bi raje uporabljali Plasma-Discover, če iščete Programsko središče.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Observera: detta omfattar inte program distribuerade via Snap eller Flatpack. Om du är ute efter ett programvarucenter, kanske du föredrar Plasma-Discover.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Зауваження: це не стосується програм, які поширюються за допомогою Snap або Flatpack. Якщо вам потрібен центр роботи із програмним забезпеченням, краще скористайтеся Plasma-Discover.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxNote: this does not include applications distributed through Snap or Flatpack. You may prefer Plasma-Discover, if what you are looking for is a Software Center.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=Muon</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=Muon</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.muon.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source" width="1600" height="900">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/muon/muon.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>muon</binary>
    <id>muon.desktop</id>
  </provides>
</component>
