<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.muon</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Muon Package Manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Gestor de paquets Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestor de paquets Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Správce balíčků Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Muon-Paketverwaltung</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Muon Package Manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Gestor de paquetes Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire de paquets Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Xestor de paquetes Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Muon pakketbeheerder</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Gestor de Pacotes Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Správca balíkov Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Muon pakethanterare</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Програма для керування пакунками Muon</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxMuon Package Managerxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Muon 软件包管理器</name>
  <summary>Search, install and remove software packages</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Cerca, instal·la i elimina paquets de programari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Cerca, instal·la i elimina paquets de programari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Software-Pakete suchen, installieren und entfernen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Search, install and remove software packages</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Buscar, instalar y eliminar paquetes de software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Buscar, instalar e retirar paquetes de software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Software pakketten zoeken, installeren en verwijderen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Pesquisar, instalar e remover os pacotes de aplicações</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Sök efter, installera och ta bort programvarupaket</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Пошук, встановлення і вилучення пакунків із програмним забезпеченням</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSearch, install and remove software packagesxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Manage applications and libraries installed on your system to the package level. Search, install and remove packages and inspect their versions and their dependences.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Gestiona les aplicacions i biblioteques instal·lades al sistema al nivell dels paquets. Cerca, instal·la i elimina paquets i les seves versions i dependències.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestiona les aplicacions i biblioteques instal·lades al sistema al nivell dels paquets. Cerca, instal·la i elimina paquets i les seues versions i dependències.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Manage applications and libraries installed on your system to the package level. Search, install and remove packages and inspect their versions and their dependences.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Gestionar aplicaciones y bibliotecas instaladas en su sistema a nivel de paquetes. Buscar, instalar y eliminar paquetes e inspeccionar sus versiones y sus dependencias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Xestionar aplicativos e bibliotecas instaladas no sistema a nivel de paquetes. Buscar, instalar e retirar paquetes e inspeccionar as súas versións e dependencias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Op uw systeem geïnstalleerde toepassingen en bibliotheken beheren op het pakketniveau. Pakketten zoeken, installeren en verwijderen en hun versies en afhankelijkheden inspecteren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Gerir as aplicações e bibliotecas instaladas no seu sistema ao nível de cada pacote. Pesquise, instale e remova os pacotes e inspeccione as suas versões e dependências.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Hantera program och bibliotek installerade på systemet på paketnivå. Sök efter, installera och ta bort paket, samt inspektera deras versioner och beroenden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Керуйте програмами і бібліотеками, встановленими у вашій системі, на рівні пакунків. Шукайте, встановлюйте та вилучайте пакунки, а також ознайомлюйтеся із версіями пакунків та їхніми залежностями.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxManage applications and libraries installed on your system to the package level. Search, install and remove packages and inspect their versions and their dependences.xx</p>
    <p>Note: this does not include applications distributed through Snap or Flatpack. You may prefer Plasma-Discover, if what you are looking for is a Software Center.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Nota: això no inclou les aplicacions distribuïdes mitjançant Snap o Flatpack. Potser preferireu el Plasma-Discover, si esteu cercant un Centre de Programari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Nota: això no inclou les aplicacions distribuïdes mitjançant Snap o Flatpack. Potser preferireu el Plasma-Discover, si esteu cercant un Centre de Programari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Note: this does not include applications distributed through Snap or Flatpack. You may prefer Plasma-Discover, if what you are looking for is a Software Centre.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Nota: esto no incluye las aplicaciones distribuidas mediante Snap o Flatpack. Es posible que prefiera usar Plasma-Discover en el caso de que esté buscando un centro de software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Nota: isto non inclúe aplicativos distribuídos mediante Snap ou Flatpack. Pode que prefira Plasma Discover, se o que busca é un centro de software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Opmerking: dit houdt geen toepassingen in gedistribueerd via Snap of Flatpack. U zou de voorkeur kunnen geven aan Plasma-Discover, als wat u zocht een Softwarecentrum is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Nota: isto não inclui as aplicações distribuídas pelo Snap ou Flatpack. Poderá preferir o Plasma-Discover, se o que precisa é um Centro de Aplicações.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Observera: detta omfattar inte program distribuerade via Snap eller Flatpack. Om du är ute efter ett programvarucenter, kanske du föredrar Plasma-Discover.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Зауваження: це не стосується програм, які поширюються за допомогою Snap або Flatpack. Якщо вам потрібен центр роботи із програмним забезпеченням, краще скористайтеся Plasma-Discover.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxNote: this does not include applications distributed through Snap or Flatpack. You may prefer Plasma-Discover, if what you are looking for is a Software Center.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=Muon</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=Muon</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.muon.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source" width="1600" height="900">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/muon/muon.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>muon</binary>
    <id>muon.desktop</id>
  </provides>
</component>
